

About Me

I am a Self confident person. I believe in hard work as it has no substitute. I learn more from my failures instead of worrying about it. I am a good team worker. I also firm. "Determination, Devotion and Discipline". I would be sincere in my work.

- 7418102661
- karthikbtech001@gmail.com.
- 8/44 Ellammal layout,
 Ondipudur, Coimbatore.

Language

- English
- Tamil

Expertise

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Problem solving ability
- Quick Learner
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Type writing
- Banking Operations

KARTHIK D

Senior Associate

Experience

Wipro technologies| Senior Associate|Medical Billing Coimbatore 2021 - 2023

Access health care|Senior client partner|Medical Billing Coimbatore 2019 - 2021

Institute of forest genetics and tree breeding Coimbatore 2016 - 2018

Karur Vysya bank | Back office Associate Coimbatore 2015 - 2016

Education

Bharathiar University

Master Business Administrative in Banking and 2021 - 2023

Bharathiar University

Master of Science in Botany 2015 - 2016

Covernment Arts College, Coimbatore

Bachelor of Science in Botany 2011 - 2014

Skills Summary

- Medical Billing
- Microsoft office
- Demo and charges
- Insurance claims
- · Clinical Documentation
- · Phyto chemical analysis